CLEL Video Oral History Project 6207 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- NAA Documentary: The Art and Science of Labor Arbitration, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Written and produced by Carol M. Rosenbaum. Final draft, revised January, 2014.
- Leaders in the Field of Women's Rights Round Table Discussion, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Janice Goodman, Susan Deller Ross, and Mary K. O'Melveny. Moderated by David R. Cashdan. March 1, 2017. Summary and Transcript.
- Kenneth E. Moffett Interview, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Summary and transcript. Interviewed by Kenneth E. Moffett, Jr. on September 25, 2017.
- Donald S. Wasserman Interview, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Summary and Transcript. Donald S. Wasserman interviewed by John E. Higgins, Jr., on November 3, 2017.
- Ray Marshall Interview, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Summary and Transcript. Interviewed by Ana Avendano on November 29, 2018.
- Roberta Golick Interview (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Transcript. Interviewed by Margaret Brogan. No date.
- Bob Walsh and Jon Hiatt Interview, 2018 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Summary and Transcript. Interviewed by Denise Mitchell on December 17, 2018.
- Interview with George Schultz, 2010 (Box 10)
  November 2, 2010.
- Interview with George Schultz, 2010 (Box 11)
- An Oral History of the Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission (OSHRC), 2011 (Box 12)
  40th Anniversary 6/2011 Panel Discussions - disc 3 of 3
- An Oral History of the Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission (OSHRC), 2011 (Box 13)
  40th Anniversary 6/2011 Panel discussions. Disc 2 of 3.
- An Oral History of the Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission (OSHRC), 2011 (Box 14)
  40th Anniversary 6/2011 Panel discussions. Disc 1 of 3
- Working for American Workers, March 4, 2009 (Box 15)
- The Art & Science of Labor Arbitration (Box 16)
- Pioneers in Labor & Employment (Box 17)
- James M. Harkless (Box 18)
  Web Excerpt
- James M. Harkless (Box 19)
  Tapes: 1-6 with Timecode
- James M. Harkless (Box 20)
  Tapes: 7-18 with Timecode
- ERISA Panel, 2012 (Box 21)
  April 13, 2012
- Labor Law Series: U. W. Clemon, Howard Jenkins, John Truesdale, Samuel Pointer, Don Banta, Warren Sullivan (Box 24)
  Transcripts.
- Labor Law Series: U. W. Clemon, Howard Jenkins, John Truesdale, Samuel Pointer, Don Banta, Warren Sullivan (Box 25)
- Labor Law Series: Judge U. W. Clemon Interview (Box 26)
- Labor Law Series: Judge U. W. Clemon Interview (Box 27)
- Labor Law Series: Howard Jenkins Interview (Box 28)
- Labor Law Series: Howard Jenkins Interview (Box 29)
- Labor Law Series: Changing the course of history the Honable Howard Jenkins, Jr. (Box 30)
- Labor Law Series: Excerpts from a Conversation with Judege U. W. Clemon (Box 31)
- Labor Law Series: Arvid Anderson (Box 32)
- Labor Law Series: Don Banta interviewed by Warren Sullivan (Box 33)
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 34)
  Disc 1 of 3
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 35)
  Disc 2 of 3
- Labor Law Series: Ted Kheel Interview (Box 36)
  Disc 3 of 3
- Labor Law Series: Samuel Pointer Interview (Box 37)
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias Interview, 2005 (Box 38)
  Switched version. December 8, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: Paul Tobias Interview, 2005 (Box 39)
  December 8, 2005.
- Labor Law Series: John Truesdale Interview (Box 40)
- Labor Law Series: Pioneers in Labor & Employment Law (Box 41)
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimmy Interview (Box 42)
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimmy Interview (Box 43)
- Labor Law Series: Max Zimmy Interview (Box 44)
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau Interview (Box 45)
  Disc 1 of 2. Switched version.
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau Interview (Box 46)
  Disc 2 of 2. Switched version.
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau Interview (Box 47)
- Labor Law Series: George Nicolau Interview (Box 48)
- Labor Law Series: Willard Wirtz Interview (Box 49)
- Labor Law Series: Frances Bairstow, "Arbitrations" Fireside Chat, 2007 (Box 50)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 51)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 52)
- Labor Law Series: William J. Usery (Box 53)
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy Interview, 2008 (Box 54)
  Disc 1 of 2. June 19, 2008. Windows burn.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy Interview, 2008 (Box 55)
  Disc 2 of 2. June 19, 2008. Windows burn.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy Interview, 2008 (Box 56)
  Disc 1 of 2. June 19, 2008.
- Labor Law Series: Betty Murphy Interview, 2008 (Box 57)
  Disc 2 of 2. June 19, 2008.
- Marvin Miller (Box 58)
  Tapes 1 & 2
- Marvin Miller (Box 59)
  Tapes 3, 4, 5
- Marvin Miller (Box 60)
  Tapes 6, 7, 8
- Marvin Miller (Box 61)
  Tapes 6, 7, 8 with time code
- Marvin Miller (Box 62)
  Tapes 3, 4, 5 with time code
- Marvin Miller (Box 63)
  Tapes 1 & 2 with time code
- Roberta Golick interviewed by Margaret Brogan (Box 64)
- Roberta Golick interviewed by Margaret Brogan (Box 65)
  Includes timecode
- Mine Safety: A conversation with Ed Clair and Davitt McAteer, 2015 (Box 66)
  Disc 1 of 2. March 11, 2015
- Mine Safety: A conversation with Ed Clair and Davitt McAteer, 2015 (Box 67)
  Disc 2 of 2. March 11, 2015.
- William Robinson interviewed by David Cashdan, 2015 (Box 68)
  Disc 1 of 2. January 19, 2015.
- William Robinson interviewed by David Cashdan, 2015 (Box 69)
  Disc 2 of 2. January 19, 2015.
- Mine Safety: A Conversation, 2015 (Box 70)
  Disc 1 of 2. March 11, 2015. Copy 2.
- Mine Safety: A Conversation, 2015 (Box 71)
  Disc 2 of 2. March 11, 2015. Copy 2.
- Judge Laurence H. Silberman interviewed by William J. Kilberg, 2015 (Box 72)
  September 16, 2015.
- Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg interviewed by William J. Kilberg, 2015 (Box 73)
  September 25, 2015.
- William H. Brown III interviewed by Patricia King, 2015 (Box 74)
  September 29, 2015.
- George Cohen Interview, 2012 (Box 75)
  June 28, 2012.
- George Cohen Interview, 2012 (Box 76)
  June 28, 2012. Copy 2.
- John E. Higgins, Jr. [part 1 of 2], 2016 (Box 78)
  Interviewed by Barry Kearney, 24Oct16
- John E. Higgins, Jr. [part 2 of 2], 2016 (Box 79)
- John E. Higgins, Jr. [part 3], 2016 (Box 80)
  Interviewed by Barry Kearney, 24Oct16. B-roll only.
- John E. Higgins, Jr. - Web Excerpt - CLEL -, 2016 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  Interviewer: Barry Kearney - Recorded: 10/24/2016. Run time: 7:03.
- CLEL Roundtable on flash drive (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Kenneth E. Moffett - 9/25/17, 2017 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Donald S. Wasserman Mediator/Arbitrator: Part 1 of 2 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Donald S. Wasserman Mediator/Arbitrator: Part 2 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 1)